Today is a very important day in our lives as Sahaja yogis.
今天對霎哈嘉瑜伽士是很重要的
This is the day when Sahasrara was opened out,
因為頂輪是在今天打開
which was really a very charismatic thing that happened.
這真是很有魅力的事件
I never expected
我從未期望
but it has been,
但卻成就了
and so many of you have got your Sahasrara opened.
你們很多人的頂輪已經打開
Without that you could never have known
若非這樣，你們不會知道
what is the truth.
甚麽是真理
You were all lost, as everybody is.
你們會像其他人一樣迷失
First of all,
首先
Sahasrara is the only way we can perceive,
頂輪是我們能察覺
understand and know the reality.
能了解，能知道實相的唯一途徑
You have come to know
你們因此知道
as to what is the reality,
甚麽是實相
and you are enjoying that state
享受自己
where you know what is the reality.
知道實相
It's a great blessing that Sahasrara was opened out
頂輪被打開是一份很大的祝福
and all of you got your realization.
你們所有人都得到自覺
Otherwise all talks are just talks
不然，任何話都只是空話
-- has no meaning,
沒有意義
has no understanding;
人理解不了
and that's why My first anxiety was to open Sahasrara.
所以為甚麽我最渴望的是打開頂輪
That worked out,
它成就到
worked out well,
成就得很好
and all of you have got
你們的頂輪
your Sahasrara opened.
全都已經打開
It's a remarkable thing.
這是很了不起的
Nobody can believe that so many of you have got
沒有人相信這麽多人的
your Sahasrara open, but I can see now clearly
頂輪已經打開，我卻可以清楚的
the light on top of your heads.
看到你們頭上的光
It is because of honest searching,
這是無庸置疑
that you have got it.
你得到了
because you were just there
你們就像
like a lamp and I just enlightened it, that's all.
一盞燈，我只是把它點亮，只是這樣
It's not such a big thing to do,
這不是甚麽大不了的事情
as you people have achieved your state,
你們已經到達了狀態
state of enlightenment,
被喚醒的狀態
that you got it because
你得到是
you were hankering after it,
因為你渴求
working it out,
你把它成就到
and you did it.
你自己做到
It's very creditable.
這是很令人敬佩的
Credit doesn't go to Me, I think,
功勞不在我
because I had a open Sahasrara,
因為我的頂輪已經打開了
but to achieve that in you people
但在你們身上成就到
was so joy-giving for Me.
也令我感到很喜樂
Now you will understand,
現在你會明白
because if Sahasrara is not open you can't talk people,
因為若頂輪還未打開，你不能向人談論
you can't say anything to them
不能向他們說甚麽
-- it's just they don't understand.
他們就是不懂
With the Sahasrara open your understanding improves so much.
頂輪打開後，你們的理解力提高了很多
That is what has happened with all of you,
這都在我們全部人身上發生
that it's so many people there are sitting here
這麽多坐在這裏的人
who have got their Sahasraras open.
的頂輪打開了
And there are many who have not come.
還有很多人還沒有來
So it's a big achievement for human beings
人類的頂輪能大規模
to get it so much collectively
集體地打開是
Sahasrara opened,
一個很大的成就
by which you know the truth,
藉此你知道真理
absolute truth.
絕對的真理
Whatever you know after your realization
得到自覺後
is the absolute truth.
你知道的都是絕對的真理
You don't argue then,
你不再爭論
don't question,
不再質疑
you just know it and you accept it
你就是知道，你接受它
as a knowledge.
為知識
It's such a nice thing that it was all there,
它在這裏是很美好的
but it was not open.
但它仍未打開
And when it opened out, how people have understood Me
當它打開後，人們就會理解我
and also the laws of the Divine.
理解上天的律法
It's such a blessing of the Divine
頂輪打開是上天
that you have got your Sahasrara opened out,
給予你的祝福
for which you may say, "We didn't do anything, Mother."
你可以說︰「母親，我們甚麽也沒有做。」
was intense and definite.
追尋是那麽熱切，那麽肯定
You wanted to know the truth,
你想知道真理
that's why it has worked out.
這就是為甚麽你能夠成就到
Otherwise no amount of money,
不然，無論多少金錢
no amount of effort,
多少努力
nothing would have helped.
都幫不了你
Sahasrara had to open by itself.
頂輪必須自己打開
It's all your building up, I should say,
全是由你所建立的。我要說
it's all your doing to yourself
是你為自己帶來
that has brought forth such a beautiful happening.
這件美麗的事情
I do not take any credit for that at all.
功勞完全不在我
Definitely I must say
我肯定的說
that I have made you understand
是我令你明白
that it's important that your Sahasrara should be opened.
你要打開頂輪是很重要的
No more arguments,
不再爭論
nothing, but have your own Sahasrara open,
只要你的頂輪打開
In these beautiful circumstances,
在這漂亮的境況下
what could your Mother say?
你的母親可以說甚麽？
I can only say that continue to live a life of reality,
我只能說你們要活在實相中
of understanding.
活在理解中
In everything you will find
每事每物你都
there is truth,
找到真理
and how do we use that truth is our own achievement.
我們怎樣運用這真理就是我們的成就
People are lost
人迷失是因為
because they have no knowledge.
他們沒有知識
Knowledge from the books is no knowledge.
從書本而來的知識不是真正的知識
Their knowledge must come from within,
知識必須來自內在
from within themselves, you see,
來自自己的內在
and that has happened because of Sahasrara opening.
你要明白，這能發生是因為頂輪打開了
In all the countries it has happened,
在很多國家，它發生了
and it will be in the whole world,
也會發生在全世界
so many people will get realization.
很多人會得到自覺
But only thing I feel that you people should have
我感到你們唯一是
no emotional attachment to it,
不要有情感的執著
not emotional but realistic attachment,
只能有對實相的執著
that it is there, it has happened, it's working out.
它就在這裏，已經發生了，已經成就了
Then you will be able to give realizations to other,
你有能力給別人自覺
you'll understand the importance of realization.
你會明白得到自覺是何等重要
Unless and until you use it
除非你運用它
you won't know what is the power of realization is.
否則你是不會知道自覺的力量
So you must learn how to use this power
所以你必須學習怎樣運用這個
which is within you,
在你內在的力量
which has started working out,
它開始運作
and which will give you such a immense capacity.
給予你這樣巨大的能耐
My health is little bit gone down -- after all, I am very old.
我的健康變差了，不管如何，我已經老了
But still I don't feel tired in any way
但當我向你演說，
while addressing you;
我仍不感到疲倦
I feel so enamored
我對有這麽多
that there are so many Sahaja yogis,
霎哈嘉瑜伽士感到很著迷
so many whose Sahasrara is opened,
那麽多的頂輪已經打開了
and they're enjoying their Sahasrara.
他們都享受他們的頂輪
Actually I would have liked you to ask Me questions,
事實上，我喜歡你們向我問問題
but you can write questions and send Me written ones.
你也可以把問題寫下寄給我
Then I'll try to answer them some time.
我會嘗試解答
Will be a much better idea.
這會是個好主意
So thank you very much.
非常感謝你們
May God bless you.
願神祝福你們
Grow into Sahaj,
希望你們能在霎哈嘉中成長
grow into your being.
在你的存有中成長
May God bless you, all My blessings.
願神祝福你們，賜給你們所有的祝福